Indiana University African Studies Program Directors' records, 1957-1995 C217
Indiana University Archives
- Correspondence, 1962-1993
  - Seminar Speakers and Lecturers, 1966-1987
    - Wells, Jerome, 1969-1970 (Box 6)
    - Welmers, William, 1970 (Box 6)
    - Whitaker, C. S., 1971 (Box 6)
    - Wol Wol, Lawrence, 1970-1971 (Box 6)
    - Wright, Marcia, 1970-1971 (Box 6)
    - Young, Crawford, 1970 (Box 6)
  - General Correspondence, 1964-1990
    - Abun-Nasr, Jamil, 1964-1965 (Box 6)
    - Alexandre, Pierre, 1966-1969 (Box 6)
    - Anderson, Lois, 1969-1970 (Box 6)
    - Ansprenger, Franz, 1970 (Box 6)
    - Ard, Josh, undated (Box 6)
    - Arlyck, Ralph, 1969 (Box 6)
    - Audu, I. S., 1966-1973 (Box 6)
    - Axelson, Eric, undated (Box 6)
    - Baylor, James, 1972-1973 (Box 6)
    - Bell, W. Herman, 1965 (Box 6)
    - Berry, Boyd, 1971-1972 (Box 6)
    - Beveridge, Andrew, 1973 (Box 6)
    - Born, Leonard, 1976 (Box 6)
    - Bridges, Roy, 1966-1970 (Box 6)
    - Bunn, Ronald, 1966-1969 (Box 6)
    - Castagno, Alphonso, 1963-1971 (Box 6)
    - DeWitt, Nicholas, 1977 (Box 6)
    - Diagne, Pathe, 1973-1974 (Box 6)
    - Dumett, Raymond E., 1971-1973 (Box 6)
    - Enenuwa, Hart, undated (Box 6)
    - Eyo, Ekpo, 1970 (Box 6)
    - Faba, Ajisafe, 1969 (Box 6)
    - Fagan, Brian, 1965-1970 (Box 6)
    - Fischer, Shirley K., 1971-1972 (Box 6)
    - Goble, Corban, 1973 (Box 6)
    - Graham-White, Anthony, 1974 (Box 6)
    - Kaser, David, 1978 (Box 6)
    - Kauffman, Robert A., 1969-1970 (Box 6)
    - Keil, Charles, 1962-1972 (Box 6)
    - Kirk-Greene, Anthony H. M., 1964-1973 (Box 6)
    - Kuper, Leo, 1972 (Box 6)
    - Larson, Charles, 1975-1978 (Box 6)
    - Leary, Fay, 1980 (Box 6)
    - Lindfors, Bernth, 1972 (Box 6)
    - Loftchie, Michael F., 1963-1972 (Box 6)
    - Loughran, John, 1986-1990 (Box 6)
    - MacGaffey, Wyatt, 1972 (Box 6)
    - Maddieson, Ian, 1972 (Box 6)
    - Mbele-Mbong, Helena, 1971 (Box 6)
    - Melson, Robert, 1973 (Box 6)
    - Mendonsa, Eugene L., 1973 (Box 6)
    - Merrill, Sally, 1972 (Box 6)
    - Miller, Joseph, 1971-1972 (Box 6)
    - Ntamere, Charles, 1973 (Box 6)
    - Nyamweya, John Moriango, 1971 (Box 6)
    - Okediji, Francis, 1967-1973 (Box 6)
    - Okumu, John J., 1972 (Box 6)
    - Opubor, Alfred, 1972 (Box 6)
    - Owomoyela, Oyekan, 1971 (Box 6)
    - Panofsky, Hans, 1962-1973 (Box 6)
    - Patel, Hasu, 1972-1973 (Box 6)
    - Pekk, Phil, 1971 (Box 6)
    - Pogozzi, Mary, 1975-1978 (Box 6)
    - Polomé, Edgar C., 1972 (Box 6)
    - Richards, Audrey, 1970-1971 (Box 6)
    - Ruhe, Robert V., 1978 (Box 6)
    - Sada, Pius O., 1971-1972 (Box 6)
    - Sampson, Ellen Grundfest, 1971 (Box 6)
    - Schmidt, Peter, 1970 (Box 6)
    - Segal, Edwin S., 1971-1972 (Box 6)
    - Sidibe, Bakari, 1972-1974 (Box 6)
    - Skinner, Nell, 1971 (Box 6)
    - Souder, Donald, 1973 (Box 6)
    - Speed, Frank, 1971 (Box 6)
    - Swanson, William, 1972 (Box 6)
    - Tomkin, Elizabeth, 1973 (Box 6)
    - Uphoff, Norman, 1969-1970 (Box 6)
    - Webster, John B., 1973 (Box 6)
    - Welch, David Baillie, 1972? (Box 6)
    - Wiseberg, Laurie, 1974 (Box 6)
- Focus: Black America Program, 1968-1969
  - Initial Planning, May-August 1968
    - Background (Box 7)
    - Focus: City Experience (Box 7)
    - Textbook Problem (Box 7)
    - General (Box 7)
    - Planning Notes (Box 7)
    - Planning (Box 7)
    - Planning Committee (Box 7)
    - Focus Outline (Box 7)
    - Indianapolis Series (Box 7)
    - Indianapolis: Budget (Box 7)
    - New Faculty (Box 7)
    - Institute for the Study of the American Negro (Box 7)
    - Focus Statement (Box 7)
  - Administration, 1968-1969
    - Afro-American Studies (Box 7)
    - Anthropology (Box 7)
    - Anthropology Museum (Box 7)
    - Bernstein, Mrs. Linda (Box 7)
      Conditions Governing Access
      File contains restricted items.
    - Bibliographies - Requests (Box 7)
    - Bookstore Reorders for Bibliographies (Box 7)
    - Campus Sources (Box 7)
    - Checklists for Speakers (Box 7)
    - Commitments - Depts., Divisions (Box 7)
    - Courses (Box 7)
    - Courses First Semester (Box 7)
    - Courses Second Semester (Box 7)
    - Dissertations (Box 7)
    - EOF Arrangement (Box 7)
    - Exhibits (Box 7)
      - Ballantine (Box 7)
      - Books (Box 7)
      - Bookstore (Box 7)
      - Fine Arts (Box 7)
      - Lilly Library (Box 7)
    - The Festival (Box 7)
    - Films (Box 7)
    - Ford Fellowships (Box 7)
    - Mailing List (Box 7)
    - Negro Colleges and Universities (Box 7)
    - Off-Campus Sources (Box 7)
    - Publicity (Box 7)
      - Clippings (Box 7)
      - Posters, (oversize) (Box OS6)
      - Posters: correspondence (Box 7)
      - Press (Box 7)
      - Radio-TV (Box 7)
      - University (Box 7)
    - Special Events (Box 7)
    - Tapes (Box 7)
    - Thank-You Notes (Box 7)
    - University Extension - Bureau of Public Discussion (Box 7)
  - Events, 1968-1969
    - Approaches to Improving the Economic Position of Black Americans (Box 7)
    - Art Exhibit (Box 7)
    - The Blacks (Box 7)
    - Black Panthers (Box 7)
    - The Black Soldier (Box 7)
    - Community Racial Integration (Box 7)
    - Economics Forum (Box 7)
    - Education School (Box 7)
    - Films (Box 7)
    - Goodbye and Good Luck (Box 7)
    - Mali Dancers (Box 7)
    - Medical Panel (Box 7)
    - The Military (Box 7)
    - The Politics of Confrontation (Box 7)
    - The Preservation Hall Jazz Band (Box 7)
    - Racial Discrimination in the Labor Market - Panel (Box 7)
    - Science Education (Box 7)
    - Science and Technology (Box 7)
    - Soul on Ice (Box 7)
    - The Spirit House Movers (Box 7)
    - Urban Ghettos and Black Americans (Box 7)
    - The Way It Is (Box 7)
  - Speakers and Performers, 1968-1969
    - Roger Abrahams (Box 7)
    - Samuel Allen (Box 7)
    - Thomas I. Atkins (Box 7)
    - Dave Baker - Concert (Box 7)
    - Barrett, David B. - Comp. Religion (Box 7)
    - Alan Bell (Box 7)
    - Julian Bond (Box 7)
    - Edward Brooke (Box 7)
    - Wilfrd Cartey (Box 7)
    - Bill Cosby (Box 7)
    - Harold Cruse (Box 7)
    - Glenna Dockery (Box 7)
    - Ivanhoe Donaldson (Box 7)
    - Edward English (Box 7)
    - Erenburg and Films (Box 7)
    - Mari Evans (Box 7)
    - Alex Haley (Box 7)
    - Roy Innis (Box 7)
    - Louis Farrakhan (Box 7)
    - Dick Gregory (Box 7)
    - David Henderson (Box 7)
    - Donald Henderson (Box 7)
    - Robert Ingram (Box 7)
    - Blyden Jackson (Box 7)
    - Johnson, John (Box 7)
    - Lerio Jones (Box 7)
    - Albert Klassen (Box 7)
    - Elizabeth Koontz (Box 7)
    - Law School (Box 7)
    - Don Lee (Box 7)
    - Myron Lieberman (Box 7)
    - Elliott Liebow (Box 7)
    - Frank Livingstone (Box 7)
    - Louis Lomax (Box 7)
    - Chase Mooney (Box 7)
    - Roy Moore (Box 7)
    - Baba Kofi Omowale (Box 7)
    - Gladys Perry (Box 7)
    - Thomas Pettigrew (Box 7)
    - Alex Poinsett (Box 7)
    - Lou Rawls (Box 7)
    - William Staff (Box 7)
    - Rockie Taylor/Larry Coleman (Box 7)
    - Arthur Tuden (Box 7)
    - Gary Wamsley (Box 7)
    - Norman E. Whitten, Jr. (Box 7)
    - Benjamin Willis/Rhody McCoy (Box 7)
- University Service, 1979-1994
  - African Exchanges, University Committee on (Box 7)
    - 1984-1988 (Box 8)
    - 1988-1989 (Box 8)
    - 1989-1991 (Box 8)
    - 1991-1993 (Box 8)
  - Archives of Traditional Music Advisory Committee (Box 8)
    - 1979-1981 (Box 8)
    - 1983-1985 (Box 8)
    - 1986-1988 (Box 8)
    - 1992-1993 (Box 8)
  - Black Film Center Archive Advisory Board, 1993 (Box 8)
  - BFC Foundation Relations (IU Foundation) (Box 8)
    - 1989-1990 (Box 8)
    - 1990-1991 (Box 8)
    - 1991-1992 (Box 8)
    - 1992-1993 (Box 8)
  - BFC Library Committee, 1989 (Box 8)
  - Canterbury Program (Box 8)
    - 1979-1983 (Box 8)
    - 1984-1985 (Box 8)
    - 1986-1992 (Box 8)
  - Center for Media and Teaching (Box 8)
    - Jan-Aug 1992 (Box 8)
    - Sep-Dec 1992 (Box 8)
    - 1993 (Box 8)
  - College of Arts and Sciences, 1979-1984 (Box 8)
  - College of Arts and Sciences, Dean Search, 1984 (Box 8)
  - Conference on South Africa for University Presidents, 1985 (Box 8)
  - Feminist Perspectives on International Conflict, 1991 (Box 8)
  - Gros-Louis, Kenneth R. R., Vice-President, 1980-1982 (Box 8)
  - IDS Publications Board (Box 8)
    - 1982-1984 (Box 8)
    - 1985-1989 (Box 8)
  - Indiana Partnership for Management Development, 1988 (Box 8)
  - Institute for Study of Performing Arts Board, 1992-1993 (Box 8)
  - International Educational Policy and Planning Ph.D., Ad Hoc Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 8)
  - International Programs, President's Council on, 1984-1992 (Box 8)
  - International Programs, Dean Search, 1993 (Box 8)
  - IU Press Faculty Advisory Committee, 1992 (Box 8)
  - Lilly Library Faculty Advisory Committee (Box 8)
    - 1992-1993 (Box 8)
    - 1993-1994 (Box 8)
    - 1994-1995 (Box 8)
  - Media Task Force, 1988-1992 (Box 8, Box 9)
  - Minority Enhancement, President's Council on, 1993 (Box 9)
  - Museum Advisory Committee (Box 9)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 9)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 9)
    - 1982 (Box 9)
    - Search and Screen, 1982 (Box 9)
    - Dedication, 1982-1983 (Box 9)
    - Dedication (working), 1983 (Box 9)
    - 1984 (Box 9)
  - Overseas Conference Fund, 1992-1993 (Box 9a)
  - Overseas Study, University Committee on, 1989 (Box 9a)
  - Performance Seminar, 1987-1989 (Box 9a)
  - Private Assistance in International Development, 1986 (Box 9a)
  - WFIU Advisory Board, 1992-1993 (Box 9a)
  - WTIU Advisory Board, 1989-1992 (Box 9a)
- Patrick O'Meara, 1974-1993
  - Pol. Sci. Committee Service, 1987-1992 (Box 9a)
  - Publications, Current History, March 1981 (Box 9a)
  - Publications, Current History, March 1984 (Box 9a)
  - SPEA: Committee Service, 1977-1992 (Box 9b)
  - SPEA: Faculty Summary Reports, 1975-1989 (Box 9b)
  - SPEA: Graduate Admissions Comm, 1990 (Box 9b)
  - SPEA: PhD. Requirements, 1989 (Box 9b)
  - SPEA: Pi Alpha Alpha Certificate, 1980 (Box 9b)
  - SPEA: Teaching Excellence Award Application, 1974 (Box 9a)
  - SPEA: Undergrad. Policy Comm., 1989-1990 (Box 9a)
  - Univ. Tenure Advisory Comm, 1990-1993 (Box 9b)
- Oversized Materials (Box 10)